A Guide to the Rockefeller foundation records, projects, SG 1.16-1.19 (A90-A93) FA469
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Rockefeller Foundation records, projects (A91), 1979-1989; 1.17; 96.19 Cubic Feet; 217 letter size document storage boxes (Boxes 1-217) 1 half legal size document storage box (Box 7A) and 1 legal size document storage box (Box 218)
  - Arts and Humanities (AH)
    - AH 8771 - Corporation for Public Broadcasting - U.S. Public Television in Africa, 1986-1987, 1989, 1992 (Box 162, Folder 911-912)
    - AH 8774 - International Arts Relations, Inc. - Playwrights' Development and Productions, 1987-1988 (Box 162, Folder 913)
    - AH 8775 - International Theatre Festival of Chicago - Cross-cultural Exchange, 1986-1988, 1990 (Box 162, Folder 914-915)
    - AH 8776 - Group I Acting Company, Inc. - "Kabuki Macbeth", 1987-1989 (Box 163, Folder 916)
    - AH 8777 - Vivian Beaumont Theater, Inc. - "Sarafina!" Documentary, 1987-1989 (Box 163, Folder 917)
    - AH 8802 - La Mama Experimental Theatre Club, Inc. - "Summer Face Woman", 1987-1990 (Box 163, Folder 918)
    - AH 8806 - Vanderbilt University - "The Cambridge History of Latin American Literature", 1987-1989 (Box 163, Folder 919)
    - AH 8807 - Spoleto Festival U.S.A. - "The Warrior Ant", 1987-1988 (Box 163, Folder 920-921)
    - AH 8807 - Spoleto Festival U.S.A. - "The Warrior Ant": [A]-- The Ant Conceived; [B]-- The Ant Concludes, From Lee Breuer and Bob Telson's "The Warrior Ant", 1987; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15628)
    - AH 8808 - Bronx Museum of the Arts - Latin American Art in the United States, 1987-1989 (Box 164, Folder 922-923)
    - AH 8808 - Bronx Museum of the Arts - Latin American Art in the United States: Supplementary Material (Box 164, Folder 924-926, Box 165, Folder 927)
    - AH 8810 - Mary Luft and Company, Inc. - 1988 New Music America Festival, 1987-1989 (Box 165, Folder 928)
    - AH 8810 - Mary Luft and Company, Inc. - 1988 New Music America Festival: Supplementary Material (Box 165, Folder 929)
    - AH 8812 - International House of Philadelphia - "Latin American Visions" Film Series, 1987-1989 (Box 165, Folder 930-931)
    - AH 8813 - New York Foundation for the Arts/Wendy Lidell - Touring Exhibition of International Film, 1986-1988 (Box 166, Folder 932-934)
    - AH 8818 - Independent Broadcasting Associates, Inc. - Radio Broadcasts on Indian Culture and Society, 1985-1989 (Box 166, Folder 935-936, Box 167, Folder 937)
    - AH 8818 - Independent Broadcasting Associates, Inc. - Radio Broadcasts on Indian Culture and Society: "Passages to India" - Program 1: A Kaleidoscope of Cultures, 1988; Sound, 59 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15629)
      Producer: Julian Crandall Hollick; Engineer: Dean Cappello
    - AH 8818 - Independent Broadcasting Associates, Inc. - Radio Broadcasts on Indian Culture and Society: "Passages to India" - Program 2: The Presence of the Past, Sound, 59 minutes; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15630)
      Producer - Julian Crandall Hollick; Engineer - Dean Cappello
    - AH 8818 - Independent Broadcasting Associates, Inc. - Radio Broadcasts on Indian Culture and Society: "Passages to India" [A]-- 1. Introduction, 2. Navayug School [B]-- 3. Durga Puja, 4. Tagore (High School version), 1987; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15631)
      Engineer - Dean Cappello; Producer - Julian Crandall Hollick
    - AH 8818 - Independent Broadcasting Associates, Inc. - Radio Broadcasts on Indian Culture and Society: "Passages to India" [A]-- 5. Rabindranath Tagore (College version), 1987; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15632)
      Engineer: Dean Cappello, Producer JUlian Crandall Hollick
    - AH 8818 - Independent Broadcasting Associates, Inc. - Radio Broadcasts on Indian Culture and Society: Supplementary Material (Box 167, Folder 938)
    - AH 8818 - Independent Broadcasting Associates, Inc. - Radio Broadcasts on Indian Culture and Society: Supplementary Material: "Passages to India", Side A: Listening to India; Vast-Humanity; Navayug School, Side B: Durga Puja; R. Tagore, 1987-1988; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15634)
    - AH 8818 - Independent Broadcasting Associates, Inc. - Radio Broadcasts on Indian Culture and Society: Supplementary Material: "Passages to India", Sides A and B: A Kaleidoscope of Cultures, 1988; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15635)
    - AH 8818 - Independent Broadcasting Associates, Inc. - Radio Broadcasts on Indian Culture and Society: Supplementary Material: "Passages to India", Sides A and B: The Presence of the Past, 1988; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15636)
    - AH 8818 - Independent Broadcasting Associates, Inc. - Radio Broadcasts on Indian Culture and Society: Supplementary Material: "Passages to India", Sides A and B: Puja; Darsan Dena; Darsan Lena, 1988; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15637)
    - AH 8818 - Independent Broadcasting Associates, Inc. - Radio Broadcasts on Indian Culture and Society: Supplementary Material: "Passages to India", Sides A and B: Gamv: Life in an Indian Village - Part One, 1988; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15638)
    - AH 8818 - Independent Broadcasting Associates, Inc. - Radio Broadcasts on Indian Culture and Society: Supplementary Material: "Passages to India", Sides A and B: Gamv: Life in an Indian Village - Part Two, 1988; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15639)
    - AH 8818 - Independent Broadcasting Associates, Inc. - Radio Broadcasts on Indian Culture and Society: Supplementary Material: "Passages to India", Sides A and B: Gamv: Life in an Indian Village - Part Three, 1988; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15640)
    - AH 8818 - Independent Broadcasting Associates, Inc. - Radio Broadcasts on Indian Culture and Society: Supplementary Material: "Passages to India", Sides A and B: Gamv: Life in an Indian Village - Part Four, 1988; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15641)
    - AH 8821 - Institute of International Education - International Arts Exchange Clearinghouse, 1988-1990 (Box 167, Folder 939)
    - AH 8826 - (The) Collective for Living Cinema, Inc. - "Misrepresentations" Film Series, 1988-1990 (Box 167, Folder 940)
    - AH 8829 - American Place Theatre, Inc. - Playwrights and Scholars Collaboration, 1986-1989 (Box 167, Folder 941)
    - AH 8830 - Association for Asian Studies, Inc. - Secondary School Teachers, 1983-1989 (Box 168, Folder 942-944)
    - AH 8831 - New York Foundation for the Arts, lnc. - Conference on Support for Artists, 1987-1990 (Box 168, Folder 945-947)
    - AH 8834 - WHYY, Inc. - INPUT (International Public Television) Conference, 1987-1989 (Box 169, Folder 948-951)
    - AH 8835 - Salzburg Seminar in American Studies, Inc. - Gender and Humanities, 1988-1989 (Box 169, Folder 952)
    - AH 8841 - Movement Theatre International, Inc. - African Artists, 1987-1990 (Box 169, Folder 953, Box 170, Folder 954)
    - AH 8844 - Associated Colleges of the Midwest - Teacher Training, 1986-1989 (Box 170, Folder 955-957)
    - AH 8845 - Pick-up Performance Company, Inc. - "MADE IN U.S.A.", 1987-1990 (Box 170, Folder 958)
    - AH 8847 - Social and Public Arts Resource Center - "World Wall", 1988-1990 (Box 171, Folder 959)
    - AH 8848 - Theatre for a New Audience, Inc. - "Shakespeare Celebration" in the Schools, 1986-1991 (Box 171, Folder 960-963)
    - AH 8850 - Oberlin College - Jazz Masterwork Editions, 1988-1990 (Box 171, Folder 964, Box 172, Folder 965)
    - AH 8850 - Oberlin College - Jazz Masterwork Editions: Jazz Masterworks: NPR Report - "All Things Considered", 1989 May 15; 1/4 inch audio cassette (Box 1, Tape AV 15633)
    - AH 8854 - Brooklyn Academy of Music - Pacific Rim Festival 1990, 1988-1990 (Box 172, Folder 966-967)
    - AH 8855 - Center for Puppetry Arts, Inc. - Festival and Conference, 1988-1991 (Box 172, Folder 968)
    - AH 8860 - California Afro-American Museum Foundation - "Introspectives: Contemporary Art by Americans and Brazilians of African Descent" Exhibition, 1987-1989 (Box 172, Folder 969, Box 173, Folder 970)
    - AH 8868 - American Music Center, Inc. - American Music Week, 1983-1990, 1992 (Box 173, Folder 971-973)
    - AH 8869 - (The) Negro Ensemble Company, Inc. - Collaborative, Evaluation, Planning, 1988-1989 (Box 173, Folder 974)
    - AH 8871 - Baltimore Theatre Project, Inc. - Teatro del Sur (Argentina) Residency, 1987-1990 (Box 174, Folder 975-976)
    - AH 8872 - City University of New York - Latin American Films, 1988, 1990 (Box 174, Folder 977)
    - AH 8874 - Hampshire College - Population Growth in Africa Workshop, 1987-1990 (Box 174, Folder 978)
    - AH 8876 - Original Ballets Foundation, Inc. - New Ballet School, 1988-1992 (Box 174, Folder 979-980)
    - AH 8880 - Great Lakes Theater Festival, Inc. - Productions, 1988-1990 (Box 175, Folder 981)
    - AH 8882 - Yale University - "Warrior Ant" Production, 1988-1989 (Box 175, Folder 982)
    - AH 8886 - New York Community Trust - Grantmakers in Arts Conference, 1988-1989 (Box 175, Folder 983)
    - AH 8887 - Colonus, Inc. "Warrior Ant" Part IV, 1988, 1990-1991 (Box 175, Folder 984)
    - AH 8896 - (The) Center for Contemporary Arts of Santa Fe, Inc. - "Ceremony of Memory" Touring, 1988-1990 (Box 175, Folder 985)
    - AH 8897 - Council on Foundations - Precollegiate Education Newsletter, 1988-1989, 1992 (Box 175, Folder 986)
    - AH 880B - Council of American Overseas Research Centers, 1985-1991 (Box 175, Folder 987, Box 176, Folder 988-991)
    - AH 880D - Museum of Contemporary Hispanic Art - Jose Campeche Exhibition, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 176, Folder 992)
    - AH 880D - Museum of Contemporary Hispanic Art - Jose Campeche Exhibition: Supplementary Material (Box 176, Folder 993, Box 177, Folder 994-995)
  - Agricultural Sciences (AS)
    - AS 8504 - Kosciuszko Foundation, Inc. - Journal Subscriptions, 1982, 1984-1986, 1988 (Box 177, Folder 996)
    - AS 8507 - Cold Spring Harbor Laboratory - Summer Course Fellowships, 1984-1987 (Box 177, Folder 997)
    - AS 8532 - Ensminger, Jean, 1985, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 177, Folder 998)
    - AS 8536 - International Trypanotolerance Centre, The Gambia - Fund Raising, 1985-1988, 1991 (Box 177, Folder 999)
    - AS 8538 - International Centre of Insect Physiology and Ecology - Social Scientist, 1985-1988 (Box 177, Folder 1000)
    - AS 8538 - International Centre of Insect Physiology and Ecology - Social Scientist, 1985-1988 (Box 178, Folder 1000A)
    - AS 8539 - International Food Policy Research Institute - Coarse Grains Project - Niger, 1985-1988, 1990 (Box 178, Folder 1001)
    - AS 8543 - Entomological Society of America - Publication Costs of Ixodid Ticks Book, 1985-1988 (Box 178, Folder 1002)
    - AS 8604 - (The) Ohio State University - Rice Pollen, 1984-1987 (Box 178, Folder 1003)
    - AS 8607 - International Centre of Insect Physiology and Ecology - Agronomist, 1986-1987 (Box 178, Folder 1004)
    - AS 8608 - American Chemical Society - Chemical Research Applied to World Needs (CHEMRAWN), 1986-1987 (Box 178, Folder 1005)
    - AS 8609 - University of Minnesota - International Congress of Plant Tissue and Cell Culture, 1986-1987 (Box 178, Folder 1006)
    - AS 8610 - McGill University - Third International Symposium on the Molecular Genetics of Plant Microbe Interactions, 1985-1987, 1989 (Box 178, Folder 1007)
    - AS 8611 - International Institute of Tropical Agriculture - Strategic Planning Study, 1986-1989 (Box 179, Folder 1008)
    - AS 8612 - University of Hawaii - Soil Taxonomy Training, China, 1985-1988 (Box 179, Folder 1009)
    - AS 8614 - University of Minnesota - Cuban Agricultural Research System, 1984-1987 (Box 179, Folder 1010)
      Formerly AS 8511
    - AS 8615 - International Center of Tropical Agriculture - Cassava Drying, Ecuador, 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 179, Folder 1011)
      Centro Internacional de Agricultura Tropical (CIAT)
    - AS 8618 - Curry Foundation - "United States Agricultural Exports and Third World Development", 1984-1988 (Box 179, Folder 1012, Box 180, Folder 1013-1015)
    - AS 8619 - National Academy of Sciences - "Managing Global Genetic Resources: Agricultural Imperatives", 1986-1988, 1991 (Box 180, Folder 1016)
    - AS 8620 - International Irrigation Management Institute - Core Budget, 1985-1987 (Box 180, Folder 1017, Box 181, Folder 1018-1019)
    - AS 8622 - International Fund for Agricultural Development - Seminar on Strengthening National Agricultural Research Systems, 1986-1989 (Box 181, Folder 1020-1021)
    - AS 8625 - International Fertilizer Development Center - Togo Office, 1986-1988 (Box 181, Folder 1022)
    - AS 8626 - International Trypanotolerance Centre - Seminar, 1986-1988 (Box 181, Folder 1023)
    - AS 8627 - Cornell University - Food Production and Availability, Africa, 1986-1988 (Box 182, Folder 1024)
    - AS 8629 - International Service for National Agricultural Research - Seminar on Management of Systems Research, 1986-1987, 1989-1992 (Box 182, Folder 1025)
    - AS 8634 - Council on Foreign Relations, Inc. - Thompson, Paul B., 1986-1990 (Box 182, Folder 1026-1027)
      Project title: "Goals of U.S. Government Assistance for Agricultural Research in the Developing World"
    - AS 8702 - (The) Brookings Institution - Politics of Agriculture, 1986-1988 (Box 182, Folder 1028)
    - AS 8703 - World Bank - African Task Force of the Consultative Group on International Agricultural Research (CGIAR), 1986-1988 (Box 182, Folder 1029)
    - AS 8705 - University of California, Davis - Gaviria, Hernan, 1987-1988 (Box 182, Folder 1030)
    - AS 8706 - New York Botanical Garden - Bibliography on Economic Uses of Palms, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 183, Folder 1031)
    - AS 8707 - International Irrigation Management Institute- Research with International Rice Research Institute (IRRI), 1986-1989 (Box 183, Folder 1032)
    - AS 8708 - International Maize and Wheat Improvement Center - Consultative Group on International Agricultural Research (CGIAR) Effort/Sub-Saharan Africa, 1987-1989 (Box 183, Folder 1033)
      Centro Internacional de Mejoramiento de Maiz y Trigo (CIMMYT)
    - AS 8710 - University of Wisconsin, Madison - Surarerks, Vanpen, 1987-1988 (Box 183, Folder 1034-1035)
      Cancelled, 7/6/87
    - AS 8711 - Institute of Development Studies, University of Sussex - Workshop on Farmers and Agricultural Research, 1987-1991 (Box 183, Folder 1036)
    - AS 8712 - International Food Policy Research Institute - International Food Policy Research Institute-Food Studies Group Workshop on Food Security Issues, 1987-1988 (Box 183, Folder 1037, Box 184, Folder 1038-1039)
    - AS 8713 - World Bank - Consultative Group on International Agricultural Research (CGIAR) African Task Force - Cassava and Maize Research, 1987-1988 (Box 184, Folder 1040)
    - AS 8714 - University of Arkansas - 1987 Farming Systems Research Symposium, 1987-1988 (Box 184, Folder 1041-1042)
    - AS 8715 - International Centre of Insect Physiology and Ecology - Household Food Production in Africa, 1986-1988 (Box 184, Folder 1043)
    - AS 8716 - Harvard University - Dejene, Alemneh, 1987-1989, 1991 (Box 185, Folder 1044-1045)
    - AS 8716 - Harvard University - Dejene, Alemneh, 1987-1989, 1991 (Box 185, Folder 1044A)
    - AS 8717 - Eicher, Carl K., 1987-1988 (Box 185, Folder 1046)
    - AS 8719 - University of the Philippines - 11th International Congress on Plant Protection, 1986-1989 (Box 185, Folder 1047)
    - AS 8721 - Centro de Ecodesarrollo - Substitution of Grains in Production, 1986-1987 (Box 185, Folder 1048)
    - AS 8722 - University of Cologne - 7th International Congress on Nitrogen Fixation, 1987-1988 (Box 185, Folder 1049)
    - AS 8725 - Overseas Development Council - Forum on International Development, 1987-1988 (Box 185, Folder 1050)
    - AS 8726 - Brown University - World Hunger Program, 1987-1991 (Box 185, Folder 1051-1052)
    - AS 8727 - Society for Plant Physiology and Biochemistry - International Congress of Plant Physiology, 1987-1989 (Box 186, Folder 1053)
    - AS 8732 - Texas A. & M. University - International Conference on Dryland Farming, 1987-1988, 1991 (Box 186, Folder 1054)
    - AS 8733 - World Bank- Workshop on Liberalizing World Trade in Agriculture, 1987-1990 (Box 186, Folder 1055)
    - AS 8801 - Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research - Conference on Biotechnology, Biological Pesticides and Novel Plant-Pest Resistance for Insect Pest Management, 1987-1989 (Box 186, Folder 1056)
    - AS 8802 - University of Georgia - Apomictic Pennisetum Species and Interspecific Hybrids, 1987-1989, 1991 (Box 186, Folder 1057)
    - AS 8804 - Muir-Leresche, Kay (Kathleen Ann), 1987-1989 (Box 186, Folder 1058)
    - AS 8808 - Inter-American Institute on Cooperation in Agriculture - Conference, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 186, Folder 1059-1060)
    - AS 8811 - Agricultural Economics Society of Southeast Asia - 7th Biennial Meeting, 1987-1992 (Box 187, Folder 1061)
    - AS 8812 - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI) - Second International Symposium on Genetic Manipulation in Crops, 1988-1990 (Box 187, Folder 1062)
    - AS 8813 - International Federation of Agricultural Producers - Adelaide Seminar and World Farmers Congress, 1987-1989, 1991 (Box 187, Folder 1063)
    - AS 8815 - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development - Underground Crops, 1988-1989 (Box 187, Folder 1064)
    - AS 8820 - Rutgers University - Agricultural Technology Management Workshop, 1988-1989 (Box 187, Folder 1065)
    - AS 8821 - University of California, Davis - International Symposium on Population Genetics and Germplasm Resources in Crop Improvement, 1988-1990 (Box 187, Folder 1066)
    - AS 8825 - Li, Liangcai, 1988-1989 (Box 187, Folder 1067)
    - AS 8828 - Bulbul, Mehmet, 1988-1989 (Box 187, Folder 1068)
    - AS 8830 - Rutgers University - Workshop on "The Markets for Vegetables in the Western Hemisphere", 1988-1989 (Box 187, Folder 1069)
    - AS 8832 - Winrock International Institute for Agricultural Development - Publications Coupon Scheme, 1988, 1990-1991 (Box 187, Folder 1070)
      Grant cancelled
    - AS 8833 - University of Arkansas - 8th Annual Farming Systems Research/Extension Symposium, 1988-1989 (Box 188, Folder 1071)
    - AS 8835 - Nongovernmental Environmental Organizations, Consultant's Report, 1988-1991 (Box 188, Folder 1072)
      "Problems of the Biosphere and the Role of United States Environmental Organizations" by Roderick Frazier Nash and Daniel Botkin
    - AS 8836 - Association of Faculties of Agriculture in Africa - Genetics Workshop, 1988-1990 (Box 188, Folder 1073)
    - AS 8837 - United Nations Development Programme - Agricultural Research at the International Level, 1987-1989, 1991 (Box 188, Folder 1074)
    - AS 8839 - University of Zimbabwe - Training Workshops in Advanced Biology, 1988-1991 (Box 188, Folder 1075)
    - AS 8840 - United Nations Development Programme - Tropical Forestry Meeting, 1988-1989 (Box 188, Folder 1076, Box 189, Folder 1077-1078)
    - AS 8841 - International Rice Research Institute (IRRI) - Nitrogen Fixation Symposium, 1988-1990 (Box 189, Folder 1079)
    - AS 8842 - Phiri, Chimimba David, 1988-1989 (Box 189, Folder 1080)
    - AS 8844 - Cool, John Cole, 1988-1989, 1991 (Box 189, Folder 1081)
      Primary grantee: Summer Institute on African Agricultural Research
  - Equal Opportunity (EO)
    - EO 8516 - Women's Commissions Research and Education Fund, Inc. - National Office, 1984-1985, 1987 (Box 189, Folder 1082)
    - EO 8517 - National Bureau of Economic Research, Inc. - Impact of Civil Rights Act on Employment, 1983-1985, 1987-1988, 1990 (Box 189, Folder 1083-1084, Box 190, Folder 1085-1086)
    - EO 8534 - University of Wisconsin - Conference on Minority Groups and Poverty, 1985-1988 (Box 190, Folder 1087-1088)
    - EO 8534 - University of Wisconsin - Conference on Minority Groups and Poverty: Supplementary Material (Box 190, Folder 1089)
    - EO 8605 - University of South Carolina - Improving Educational Research Opportunities for Minorities and Women, 1985-1987 (Box 191, Folder 1090)
    - EO 8608 - Women's Research and Education Institute - Health Care Conference Proceedings, 1986-1987 (Box 191, Folder 1091)
    - EO 8609 - (The) Urban Institute - Underclass Issues, 1986-1988 (Box 191, Folder 1092-1093)
    - EO 8610 - Baylor College of Medicine - Minority Apprenticeships, 1982-1988 (Box 191, Folder 1094)
      Formerly 200
    - EO 8610 - Baylor College of Medicine - Minority Apprenticeships: Supplementary Material (Box 192, Folder 1095)
    - EO 8610 - Baylor College of Medicine - Minority Apprenticeships: Supplementary Material: "The Art and Science of Magnet Schools", 1983 January 10; Sound, Color, 21 minutes; U-matic (Box 2, Tape AV 12044)
      UT-TV Houston - Network for the Health Sciences, The University of Texas Health Science Center. Robert E. Roush, Director - Center for Allied Health Professions, Baylor College of Medicine.
    - EO 8611 - National Commission on Jobs and Small Business, 1986-1987 (Box 192, Folder 1096)
      Primary grantee: National Development Council
    - EO 8613 - (The) Institute for Journalism Education - Conference, 1986-1988 (Box 192, Folder 1097)
    - EO 8614 - Dash, Leon, 1986-1989 (Box 192, Folder 1098)
      Book: "When Children Want Children: The Urban Crisis of Teenage Childbearing"
    - EO 8615 - Florida International University - Service Credit Concept, 1986-1987 (Box 192, Folder 1099)
    - EO 8616 - Program to Address Problems of the Urban Underclass, 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 192, Folder 1100)
      To enable the Joint Center for Political Studies to assist the RF in developing plans to address critical problems of the urban underclass
    - EO 8619 - Institute for Puerto Rican Policy, Inc. - Latinas in the United States, 1984, 1986-1989 (Box 193, Folder 1101)
    - EO 8620 - Washington Urban League, Inc. - National Conference on Educating Black Children, 1986-1989 (Box 193, Folder 1102)
    - EO 8621 - Northwestern University - Random Assignment Process, 1986-1988 (Box 193, Folder 1103-1105)
    - EO 8622 - Catholic University of America - Young Unwed Fathers, 1986-1988 (Box 194, Folder 1106-1107)
    - EO 8622 - Catholic University of America - Young Unwed Fathers: Supplementary Material (Box 194, Folder 1108-1109)
    - EO 8623 - National Academy of Sciences - Prenatal Care and High Risk Pregnancies, 1986-1988 (Box 194, Folder 1110, Box 195, Folder 1111-1114)
    - EO 8626 - Northern California Grantmakers - Hispanics in Philanthropy, 1985-1988 (Box 195, Folder 1115, Box 196, Folder 1116)
    - EO 8628 - Yale University - Social Welfare Policy, 1986-1989, 1992 (Box 196, Folder 1117)
    - EO 8630 - University of Minnesota, Hubert H. Humphrey Institute of Public Affairs - Venture Capital and Job Development Strategies in the Black Community, 1986-1988 (Box 196, Folder 1118)
    - EO 8631 - Program to Address Problems of the Urban Underclass - Economic Framework Report, 1986-1988 (Box 196, Folder 1119)
    - EO 8632 - National Committee Against Discrimination in Housing - Housing Mobility, 1986-1990 (Box 196, Folder 1120, Box 197, Folder 1121-1122)
    - EO 8633 - (The) Rand Corporation - Youth Policy and Juvenile Delinquency, 1986-1989 (Box 197, Folder 1123-1124)
    - EO 8634 - Cleveland Tomorrow - Urban Neighborhoods, 1986-1988 (Box 197, Folder 1125)
    - EO 8636 - Mississippi Action for Community Education - Financial Analysis and Economic Stabilization Project, 1986-1988, 1992 (Box 198, Folder 1126-1127)
    - EO 8637 - National Board of the YWCA of the U.S.A. - Soviet Women's Committee Visit, 1986-1987, 1989 (Box 198, Folder 1128)
    - EO 8638 - City University of New York - Literacy Education, 1984-1990 (Box 198, Folder 1129-1130, Box 199, Folder 1131-1135, Box 200, Folder 1136-1138)
      Formerly EO 8501
    - EO 8638 - City University of New York - Literacy Education, 1984-1990 (Box 200, Folder 1139)